<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<posts>
  <post>
    <id>1</id>
    <title>Top Mop Robot to Keep Your Floor Sparkling</title>
    <date>2022-01-01</date>
    <author>John Doe</author>
    <summary>While they're not a necessity by any means, it's pretty awesome that robots can clean our floors. It's even cooler when the technology...</summary>
    <a>https://www.seasonsincolour.com/post/top-mop-robot-to-keep-your-floor-sparkling</a>
    <image>https://static.wixstatic.com/media/5bcfac_e48b317096894e88973693bf029d9cfb~mv2.jpeg/v1/fill/w_481,h_550,fp_0.50_0.50,q_90,enc_auto/5bcfac_e48b317096894e88973693bf029d9cfb~mv2.jpeg</image>
    <body>
        While they're not a necessity by any means, it's pretty awesome that robots can clean our floors. It's even cooler when the technology has advanced enough to allow the vacuum and the mop to work together. The mop will come out after the vacuum has done its job and remove any dirt that was missed. Now your robot can clean every inch of your home from top to bottom!
        But if you don't have many carpeted spaces, a stand-alone mop robot may be enough. It can focus more on wiping the floor better. This feature is what makes the bot very popular these days. Also, they are getting smarter each year. Some models only need 10% human intervention - the rest are up to the bot. Automatic bots don't just make your life easier; they can also lower electric bills.
        Here is our list of the best mop robot for this year:
        Roborock S7 MaxV
        All of the hardware improvements that come with the previous Roborock S7 are also present in the MaxV model. When mopping, the VibraRise mop component vibrates to effectively scour the floor and eliminate embedded spots and smudges. This prevents spreading them across the surface. 
        To avoid soaking the carpets, it also rises by 5mm when it detects them. It now has an all-rubber brush for easy cleaning. The brush's height may be adjusted to effectively scour uneven surfaces and remove dust from carpets. Among all other models, the Roborock S7 MaxV vacuum and mop robot is a must have for a smart home.
    </body>
  </post>
  <post>
    <id>2</id>
    <title>MDecorate with the new Farrow  Ball palette</title>
    <date>2022-02-01</date>
    <author>Jane Smith</author>
    <summary>There is always a sense of anticipation when colour paint giant Farrow and Ball release their new palettes.</summary>
    <a>https://www.seasonsincolour.com/post/how-to-decorate-with-the-new-farrow-and-ball-colour-palette</a>
    <image>https://static.wixstatic.com/media/5bcfac_6277fc6d92b447b0bffbf3aa36d02511~mv2.jpeg/v1/crop/x_0,y_143,w_980,h_1207/fill/w_630,h_776,al_c,q_85,usm_0.66_1.00_0.01,enc_auto/How%20to%20decorate%20with%20the%20new%20Farrow%20and%20Ball%20colour%20palette.jpeg</image>
    <body>
      There is always a sense of anticipation when colour paint giant Farrow and Ball release their new palettes. In September 2022, 11 new colours were introduced that will influence the way we decorate our homes for years to come. Let's have a look at these beautiful colours and how they can be used. 
      Stirabout by Farrow and Ball
      Stirabout is inspired by the nurturing porridge favoured over many centuries in Ireland. An earthy tone with just a hint of underlying grey, it’s perfect for creating a relaxed feel, which will never be too cold. Try pairing it with Jitney and natural fabrics for a laidback look.
      Recommended Primer and Undercoat: White and Light Tones
      Complementary white: Pointing
      Eddy - the gentle green
      A gentle green named after the circular currents enjoyed by wild water swimmers as a natural jacuzzi. This evocative colour creates a seamless connection with nature, perfect for use in a garden room or alongside natural materials. A breath of fresh air, Eddy is also an ideal choice for calm, relaxing spaces. It is delicate in tone without crossing into pastel and sits at the lightest end of the French Gray and Treron family.
    </body>
  </post>
  <post>
    <id>3</id>
    <title>Small Business Tips</title>
    <date>2022-03-01</date>
    <author>Bob Johnson</author>
    <summary>You don't need to spend a fortune to market your small business. Get these tips on website building, online marketing and more to grow your business.</summary>
    <image>https://static.wixstatic.com/media/46e2e0_ce1a5eb7454e41c5a9b8afbf1be4cc0a~mv2.png/v1/fill/w_1064,h_607,al_c,q_90,enc_auto/46e2e0_ce1a5eb7454e41c5a9b8afbf1be4cc0a~mv2.png</image>
    <a>https://www.wix.com/blog/2019/11/business-plan-template-step-by-step-guide/</a>
    <body>
      There’s a difference between deciding it’s a good idea to start a business and actually bringing it to fruition. You will need to take several steps to make it official, such as registering your business and creating a business website. Another quite large leap to truly test your commitment is to write a business plan.
      This document will allow you to formulate your ideas into a streamlined and organized process, as well as set goals for your future. With this business plan template guide, you’ll be able to get started on your very own right away.
      A business plan is a written document used by SMBs, entrepreneurs and other new ventures when starting a business. It serves several purposes, such as attracting potential partners, as well as investors and banks when it comes to raising capital. Most importantly though, you’ll be able to use your business plan as a roadmap for how to structure, operate and manage your new venture. 
    </body>
  </post>
</posts>
